时间
Time.
空间
Space.
现实
Reality.
这并非一条直线
It's more than a linear path.
而是一块包含无限可能的棱镜
It's a prism of endless possibility,
一个选择就能折射出无限的现实
where a single choice can branch out into infinite realities,
创造出与你所知相去甚远的世界
creating alternate worlds from the ones you know.
我是「观察者」
I am the Watcher.
我是这片广袤新世界的导游
I am your guide through these vast new realities.
跟着我，思考这个问题…
Follow me and ponder the question...
"假如?"
"What if?"
星期一
有个想法是召集一群…
There was an idea to bring together a group of…
杰出之人?
Remarkable people?
看看他们是否能变得更伟大?
To see if they could become something more?
我知道。我听过这个演讲
I know. I've heard the speech.
那你就会意识到这关系着什么
Then you realize what's at stake.
那我就纳闷了，你怎么会
Which is why I'm surprised you'd wanna bet
把复仇者计划的未来压在他身上?
the future of the Avengers Initiative on that.
斯塔克可能有点怪，但他很有潜力
Stark may be eccentric, but he's got potential.
只会宿醉的潜力?
What he's got is a hangover.
我有没有告诉过你一件事
Did I ever tell you about this one time
我将一名俄罗斯刺客招募进了我的美国秘密行动小组?
I actually recruited a Russian assassin to join my American covert ops team?
有点印象
Vaguely rings a bell.
那你应该知道，我不怕冒险
Then you should know, I'm not afraid of a big swing.
先生，我得请你离开那个「甜甜圈」
Sir, I'm going to have to ask you to exit the donut.
我告诉过你，我不想加入你的「超级秘密男孩乐队」
I told you I don't wanna join your super-secret boyband.
不，不，不。看，我记得，你一直独来独往
No, no, no. See, I remember, you do everything yourself.
-你觉得怎么样? -更糟了
-How's that working out for you? -I've been worse.
你成了一个问题，一个我必须处理的问题
You've become a problem, a problem I have to deal with.
与你的信念相反，你并不是我的宇宙中心
Contrary to your belief, you are not the center of my universe.
-我明白了 -打他
-I get it. -Hit him.
天啊，她刚才对我做了什么?
God. What'd she just do to me?
我们刚才为你做了什么?
What did we just do for you?
那是二氧化锂。能让你轻松一阵
That's lithium dioxide. It's gonna take the edge off.
这治标…不治本?
It's not a cure, it just abates the symptoms?
斯塔克！你没事吧?
Stark! You okay?
-斯塔克！-托尼，托尼!
-Stark! -Tony. Tony!
他死了
He's dead.
人类，如此渴望，如此愿意面对不可能
Humanity, so eager, so willing to face the impossible,
但对大局却视而不见
yet blind to the bigger picture.
在一周之内，分别展开了三个奇怪的故事
Inside one week, three strange and separate stories unfolded.
一个天才与他的恶魔，由内至外地斗争
A genius battled his demons both inside and out,
同时，世界见到了那个藏于人内的怪物
while the world met the monster hiding in the man.
一位神圣的王子「降临」人间
And a godly prince fell to Earth.
我是「观察者」
I am the Watcher.
在人类看到混乱的地方
And where humans see chaos,
我看到了会将「个人集合」
I see the crucible that would transform
转化为「英雄团队」的严酷考验
this collection of individuals into a team of heroes.
至少在某个宇宙中，事情是这样发展的
At least, that's how things played out in one universe.
但在这个宇宙中…
But in this one...
星期二
长官，我们找到它了
Sir, we found it.
我正忙着呢，考森
Kind of in the middle of something here, Coulson.
应该不能再等了，长官。当地人越来越好奇了
Not sure it can wait, sir. Locals are getting curious.
设置警戒线，告诉小队我在路上
Set up a perimeter and tell the team I'm en route.
我可能不是托尼·斯塔克的粉丝，但我没有杀他
I may not have been a fan of Tony Stark, but I didn't kill him.
把你的说辞留给皮尔斯吧
Save your spin for Pierce.
他要你立即去纽约接受审问
He wants you in New York first thing for questioning.
能给我们一分钟吗?
Wanna give us a minute?
不关我的事
This wasn't me.
我知道，但是神盾局有协议
I know that, but S.H.I.E.L.D. has protocols,
所以我的手和你的一样被绑住了
so my hands, like yours, are tied.
-你知道，他们抓不住我的 -哦，我就指望它了
-You know these won't hold me. -Oh, I'm counting on it.
神盾局内部有人泄露了斯塔克的解药
Someone inside S.H.I.E.L.D. compromised Stark's antidote.
旁观者清，我需要有人在外面找出是谁
I need someone on the outside to find out who.
你确定想再冒一次险吗，老板?
Sure you wanna take another big swing on me, boss?
我做过的最安全的赌注
Safest bet I'll ever make.
哇！太严肃了
Wow. So serious.
也许我们应该放一些曲子
Maybe we should get some tunes going.
放松心情
Lighten the mood.
你们真没意思。介意帮我拿下吗?
You guys are no fun. Here. Mind holding these for me?
当然，额…什么鬼?
Of course. Uh... What?
我一直不明白他看上她哪一点
I never did get what he sees in her.
当然，她能打出一拳，但只是因为人们没有预料到
Sure, she can land a punch, but only 'cause people don't expect it.
什么？停！停车!
What? Stop! Stop the truck!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
哦！草了!
Oh! Come on!
普恩特安提奎，新墨西哥州
据我们所知，它非常强大，不是地球之物
Best we can tell, it's extremely powerful and not from around here.
电磁辐射，中子辐射，维塔辐射，全部爆表
Electromagnetic, neutron, vita radiations, all off the charts.
嗯，听起来不妙啊
Well, that doesn't sound ominous at all.
整晚都这样
It's been happening all night.
这个东西有自己的想法
The artifact has a bit of an attitude.
而且，没人能举起它
Also, no one can lift it.
就连在做体能训练的杰克逊也不行
Not even Jackson and he does CrossFit.
丢了如此强大的东西，总会有人来找的
Something that powerful goes missing, someone always comes looking.
我们只需要祈祷那个人是我们的朋友
We just have to cross our fingers that someone is an ally.
那，如何行动?
So, what's the move?
一如既往。抱最好的希望，做最坏的打算
Same as always. Hope for the best, prepare for the worst.
有人被袭击了。发出警报
We got a man down. Sound the alarms.
我想最坏的情况来了
I think the worst just got here.
考森，汇报
Coulson, talk to me.
有人突破了警戒，袭击了多位特工并且…
We got a perimeter breach. Multiple agents down and...
哇
Whoa.
我看到入侵者了
I got visual on the intruder.
白人男性，20 多岁，有…
He's a Caucasian male, mid-twenties with...
一头靓发
really great hair.
啥?
Excuse me?
我没瞎说，长官，他很帅
It's an accurate description. Sir, he's gorgeous.
-我需要天上的眼睛，巴顿 -已经开始了
-I need eyes in the sky. Barton. -Already on it.
他正在移动锤子
He's making a move on the hammer.
一枪一个，长官，下命令吧
One shot, one kill, sir. Just say the word.
别开火。我想看看
Hold your fire. I wanna see this.
哇。考森没瞎说，头发确实不错
Whoa. Coulson wasn't lying about the hair. That's nice.
弗瑞，机不可失
Fury, now or never.
别开…
Hold your…
该死，巴顿。我跟你说了待命
Damn it, Barton. I told you to stand down.
是的！不是我！我没有开火！
I did! Wasn't me! I didn't shoot!
放下武器!
Drop your weapon!
我发誓，我没开火
I swear, I didn't shoot.
你的箭可不这样
Your arrow would indicate otherwise.
这说不通，我从不手滑，我没有走火
This doesn't make any sense. I don't slip. I don't misfire.
-入侵者什么情况？-死了
-What's the word on our intruder? -Dead.
如果他的血样可信
And if his blood samples are to be believed,
他快一千岁了，并且不属于这个世界
he's almost a thousand years old and not of this world.
先是斯塔克，现在是肌肉男
First Stark, now Muscle Beach.
24 小时，两个重要目标死在了我们神盾局特工手里
That's two high value S.H.I.E.L.D. targets killed by our own agents inside 24 hours.
-巴顿坚持他的说法？-他气坏了
-Barton's sticking to his story? -He's pretty bent out of shape.
-不会跟任何人说话的 -他会跟我说的
-Won't talk to anyone. -He'll talk to me.
醒醒，睡美人
Wake up, Sleeping Beauty.
巴顿
Barton.
巴顿。考森，叫医生来
Barton. Coulson, get a medic.
这怎么可能…你让谁进来过?
How could this... Who did you let in here?
-没人 -没人
-No one. -No one.
坚持住，坚持住
Stay with me. Stay with me.
我们正在做毒物检测，看看是不是氰化物胶囊
We're running a tox screen to see if it was a cyanide capsule.
巴顿已经有妻子和孩子了
Barton had a wife and kids.
他肯定不是自杀
If he was gonna go, it wouldn't be willingly.
你认为他是被谋杀的
You think he was murdered.
我猜，与杀死斯塔克的是同一人
If I had to guess, my money is on the same someone who killed Stark.
但巴顿被关在一间被监视的牢房里
But Barton was in a locked cell under observation.
没有挣扎的迹象，也没有伤口
There was no sign of struggle, no entry wounds.
这很奇怪，但我也有一具正在那边腐烂的
It's weird, but I also have a space corpse
看起来像是「奇彭德尔舞者」的太空尸体
that looks like a Chippendales dancer rotting on the next table over.
哦，哇
Oh, wow.
即使在腐烂，他也闻起来像薰衣草
Even while rotting, he smells like lavender.
真的?
Really?
嗯
Mmm.
尽管如此，他跟身为亿万富翁的花花公子也没啥关系
Still, there's not a lot connecting a billionaire playboy
更别说神盾局刺客了，你怎么看?
and a S.H.I.E.L.D. assassin, unless you have any ideas.
我有个主意
There was an idea.
星期三
卡尔弗大学，弗吉尼亚州
罗斯博士，不知道你是否还记得我，但是…
Dr. Ross. Not sure if you remember me, but…
哦，我记得
Oh, I remember.
我还是那句话
And I'll tell you the same thing I told you
就像上次神盾局来这那样
the last time S.H.I.E.L.D. came poking around.
我没见过他
I haven't seen him.
我不是为了那个绿家伙来这的
I'm not here about the green guy.
他的名字是布鲁斯·班纳博士，我很忙，罗曼诺夫特工
His name is Dr. Bruce Banner. And I'm in a rush, Agent Romanoff.
我来这里是为了托尼·斯塔克，我相信他是被谋杀的
I'm here about Tony Stark. I believe he was murdered.
什么？谁干的?
What? By whom?
我。或者说，至少有人想用这个栽赃给我
Me. Or at least someone's trying to make it look that way, using this.
那你为什么来找我?
So, why did you come to me?
你是细胞生物学战术应用方面的专家
You're an expert in the tactical applications of cellular biology.
又不止我一个，你到底是来干什么的?
There are plenty of others. Why did you really come here?
我不能让神盾局发现
I need to keep this off S.H.I.E.L.D.'s radar
而你似乎很有经验
and you seem to have some experience in that department.
嗯。你的注射器是干净的
Mmm. Well, your injector's clean
没有任何致命病原体的痕迹
and there's no traces of lethal pathogens of any kind.
那是什么杀了他?
Then what killed him?
不管是什么，肯定不是生物学上的
Whatever it was, it wasn't biological.
你的解药甚至没有从注射器里出来
Your antidote didn't even make it out of the syringe.
在我看来，这像是从针头发射出了一颗极小子弹
It looks to me like a tiny projectile of some kind was fired from the needle.
你是说纳米技术?
You're thinking nanotech?
我是生物学家，不是弹道专家
I'm a biologist, not a ballistics expert.
我觉得你该走了
And I believe we're done here.
呵呵。你有兼职吗，罗斯博士?
Huh. You got a side job, Dr. Ross?
什么？我不知道。我…
What? I don't know. I...
一定是哪个学生忘在这的
A student must have left it there.
一个坏消息，还有一个更坏的消息
I got bad news and worse news.
-你在一个安全的地方吗 -目前还没有
-You in a secure location? -Not currently.
巴顿死了
Barton's dead.
我知道他对你意味着什么
I know what he meant to you.
谁 干 的 ?
Who do I kill?
看来他和斯塔克的谋杀案有关联
Looks like his and Stark's murders are connected.
-凭什么 -复仇者计划
-By what? -The Avengers Initiative.
看来凶手在追捕候选人
Seems our killer is going after the candidates.
如果有人想攻击神盾局
If someone wanted to kneecap S.H.I.E.L.D.,
这是一个很好的切入点
that's a good place to start.
名单上还有谁?
Who else is on the list?
说的就是这个，布鲁斯·班纳和你
That's the thing. Bruce Banner and you.
在其他的情况下，我会受宠若惊，克林特也是
Under different circumstances, I'd be flattered. So would Clint.
你得躲起来。但首先，找到班纳
You need to get yourself to ground. But first, find Banner.
真有趣，老板。我想我已经找到了
Funny thing, boss. Think I already have.
对…对不起，我不能让你进去
I... I'm sorry, but I can't let you in there.
滚开，不然我就帮你滚开
Move, or I'll make you move.
用不上暴力，罗曼诺夫特工
No need for violence, Agent Romanoff.
那可能行不通，对任何人来说
That's probably not gonna work out. For anyone.
什么？怎么了?
What? What is it?
我们得走了，现在
We need to go. Now.
考森，你在哪?
What's your 20, Coulson?
咖啡馆，休息一下
Coffee run. Needed a breather.
给你弄了个双倍黑糖玛奇朵，就是你喜欢的那种
Got you a double macchiato. Just how you like it.
什么鬼…
What the...
局长，传感器报告有一股巨大的能量浪潮
Director, sensors are reporting a massive energy surge.
-好像是凭空出现的 -考森，你看到什么了吗?
-Seems like it came out of nowhere. -What are you seeing, Coulson?
某种气象现象
A meteorological phenomenon of some kind.
哦，完了。不管是什么，都来者不善
Oh, boy. Whatever it is, it came with bogeys.
-他们看起来是地球人吗？-也许是中土世界?
-They look like they're from Earth? -Maybe Middle-earth?
去抓他们，老板
Go get 'em, boss.
先生，您在找方向吗？因为你好像迷路了
Looking for directions, sir? Because you seem to have lost your way.
你最好在神的面前跪下
You would do best to kneel before a god.
我们这可没这种习俗，无论你是谁
We don't really do that here. No matter who or what you are.
-我是洛基，阿斯加德的王子
I am Loki, Crown Prince of Asgard.
约顿汉姆的合法…
The rightful king of Jotun…
国王。诡计…
Jotunheim. And God of M--
之神。你要接吗？我现在正忙着呢
Mischief. Are you gonna take that? I'm in the middle of something.
该死，弗瑞！接啊
Damn it, Fury! Pick up.
嘿，我跟你说，我自己照顾自己对大家都更安全
Hey, I'm telling you, it's safer for everyone if I fend for myself.
-我死不了的 -那你走运了
-I sort of can't die. -Then I guess you're in luck.
保持警戒
Look alive, people.
我要突击队就位，准备就绪，听我命令就行动
I want strike teams locked, loaded, and ready to move in on my mark.
我有点忙，黑寡妇
I'm a little busy here, Widow.
哦，很好。我们将成立一个互助小组
Oh, good. We'll start a support group.
我这有罗斯将军，一打狙击手和几辆坦克
I've got General Ross, a dozen snipers and a few tanks.
-你那边呢？-星际强盗
-What are you dealing with? -Space Vikings.
-吹牛 -你处理好那边，然后躲起来
-Show-off. -Handle it, then get to ground.
女人麻烦?
Lady trouble?
你来这干什么，洛基先生?
Well, what exactly is it that brought you here, Mr. Loki?
复仇
Vengeance.
这个星球的一名特工谋杀了阿斯加德的王子，索尔·奥丁森
An agent of this planet murdered Thor Odinson, the Crown Prince of Asgard.
娜塔莎·罗曼诺夫，神盾局特工
Natasha Romanoff, agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
布鲁斯·班纳在我的监管之下，你们退下
I have Bruce Banner in my custody. You need to stand down.
-嘿，嘿！别开枪 -谁他妈开的枪?
-Hey, hey! Don't shoot! -Who the hell opened fire?
不是我们，先生
Not us, sir.
布鲁斯！没关系。没事的，对吧?
Bruce! It's okay. We're okay, right?
我会把你救出去的，我以我的性命发誓
I'll get you out of this. I swear on my life.
弗瑞局长，你没能理解形势的严重性
Director Fury, you fail to comprehend the enormity of the situation.
哦，我明白了，好吧
Oh, I'm comprehending, all right.
罗曼诺夫特工，我想你最好离开这里
Agent Romanoff, I think you might be better off getting out of here.
我要问一下，盒子里是什么?
Which is why I have to ask, what's in the box?
哦
Ooh.
这种傲慢是不能容忍的
Such insolence will not be tolerated.
作为报复，你的星球将毁灭
And your planet will be taken as retribution.
干掉他!
Take it down!
哦，你想吃枪子吗？来吧
Oh, you want some of this? Come on!
爸爸！停，停，停下来!
Father! No! Stop! Stop, please!
停!
Stop!
-你无能为力 -那是我父亲，他会听我的话的
-There's nothing you can do. -That's my father. He'll listen to me.
将军不是这件事的始作俑者
The General isn't the one who started this.
那是谁干的?
Then who did?
布鲁斯!
Bruce!
不，不，不，不，布鲁斯
No. No, no, no. Bruce.
但他是不死的。他不会死的
But he can't die. He can't die.
他不会
He can't.
向这个星球宣战可带不会你的王子!
Declaring war on this planet will not bring your prince back!
等一下
Wait.
他没说错。奥丁也希望我们能听一下
He's not wrong. The All-Father would want us to listen.
我们有共同的敌人
We have the same enemy here.
杀你哥哥的人，也杀了我的两个人
The person who killed your brother also killed two of my people.
都是好人。我们应该一起努力
Good people. We should be working together.
我们不是盟友
We are not allies.
那我来帮你
Then let me help you.
我保证，当我找到杀害你哥哥的凶手
I promise, when I find your brother's killer,
你会获得他的「一磅肉」的
you will have your pound of flesh.
多么美妙的词语啊
What a fascinating choice of words.
不过我要整具尸体
But I shall require the entire corpse.
你得给我时间
You need to give me time.
可以
Very well.
米德加德（地球）的日出之前，把杀害我哥哥的凶手带到我面前
You have until the next rise of Midgard's sun to deliver my brother's assassin,
否则我会把这个星球变成灰烬和冰霜
or I will reduce this planet to ash and ice.
马纳萨斯，弗吉尼亚州
你为什么需要我的密码?
Why do you need my password?
我需要查看复仇者计划的档案
I need to get into the Avengers Initiative files,
但我被系统拒之门外，因为谋杀而被通缉
but I'm locked out of the system and wanted for murder.
我不会告诉你我的密码的，罗曼诺夫。
I'm not telling you my password, Romanoff.
-为什么不？-因为我不是（那种人）
-Why not? -Because I'm not.
考森，克林特也是你的朋友
Coulson. Clint was your friend, too.
哈希标签：史蒂夫×3，我爱史蒂夫，0704（密码翻译）
Hashtag-Steve-Steve-Steve- I-heart-Steve-0-7-0-4.
哇!
Wow.
-好的，考森 -咋了?
-Good one, Coulson. -What?
不，没什么。太好了。非常感谢
No, nothing. That's great. Thank you.
呵呵。一个两年前就已经死去的女人
Huh. How did a woman who died two years ago
是怎么在昨天访问数据库的?
access the database yesterday?
你不会赢的，赢不了我，也赢不了神盾局
You won't win. Not against me. Not against S.H.I.E.L.D.
你找到我了，你知道该怎么做
You found me. You know what to do.
弗瑞，是希望！是希望!
Fury, it's Hope! It's all about Hope!
是希望！是希望!
It's Hope! It's all about Hope!
还有四小时就要日出了，先生
Four hours to sunup, sir.
我没忘
I haven't forgotten.
长官，我知道，洛基王子就是你
Sir, I understand that this Prince Loki situation is the very reason
提出复仇者计划的原因
you proposed the Avengers Initiative
来让一群杰出之人打赢一场不可能的战争
for a group of remarkable individuals to fight the battles we can't.
我写的演讲稿
I wrote the speech.
还有一个人，长官
There's still one name left, sir.
你
Yours.
我不是最后一个复仇者
I'm not the only Avenger left.
什么?
What?
那是 90 年代的传呼机吗?
Is that a beeper from the '90s?
也是我们最后的希望
Also our last hope.
"希望，是希望"
"Hope. It's all about Hope."
黑寡妇
Widow.
老板?
Boss?
-你要去哪里? -不确定
-Where are you going? -Not sure.
要么与天神订契约，要么与恶魔做交易
Either make a pact with a god or deal with a devil.
你叫什么，士兵?
You got a name, soldier?
我是来见你老板的
I'm here to see your boss.
星期四
旧金山，加利福尼亚州
霍普（希望）
（珍妮特）·凡·戴恩
亲爱的女儿，神盾局特工
这不是汉克·皮姆吗?
If it isn't Hank Pym.
你还有胆子来这，站在她的碑前
The balls you have to come here and stand over her grave.
哦，别担心她
Oh, don't worry about her.
我觉得她不会介意的，考虑到她已经死了
I doubt she'd mind, considering she's dead.
神盾局杀了她
She died because S.H.I.E.L.D. killed her.
她是因为你而死的
She died because of you.
霍普·凡·戴恩特工是在乌克兰的奥德赛郊外执行任务时遇害的
Agent Hope Van Dyne was killed on a mission outside Odessa, Ukraine.
特工?
Agent?
她是我的女儿！我亲爱的女儿
She was my daughter! My little girl.
她想念她的母亲，而你利用了这一点!
She missed her mother and you exploited that!
她母亲是特工?
Her mother was an agent?
别跟我开玩笑了，弗瑞
Don't play the fool with me, Fury.
你在她的脑子里塞满了关于保护人类和拯救世界的废话
You filled her head with nonsense about protecting humanity and saving the world.
你忘了她是怎么死的，就像她妈妈一样
You just left out how she died the same way her mother did,
替神盾局做那些肮脏的工作!
doing S.H.I.E.L.D.'s dirty work!
这就是你杀他们的理由吗?
And that gave you permission to murder them?
安东尼·斯塔克？克林特·巴顿？布鲁斯·班纳？娜塔莎·罗曼诺夫？
Anthony Stark? Clint Barton? Bruce Banner? Natasha Romanoff?
你拿走了我的一切
You took everything from me.
我要让你遭到报应
I wanted you to hurt.
见证你为之工作的一切…
To witness everything you've ever worked for...
为…而战的…
fought for...
希望…
hoped for...
死亡
die.
那阿斯加德王子索尔呢?
And what of Thor, Prince of Asgard?
金发女孩吗？你会毫不犹豫地招募他
Goldilocks? You would have recruited him in a heartbeat.
向他兜售一些成为英雄的花言巧语
Sold him some malarkey about being a hero.
你就是这么做的，就像神盾局一直以来做的那样
That's what you do. What S.H.I.E.L.D. has always done.
找别人替你战斗
Find others to fight your battles.
就这样？你杀了他只是因为你可以?
That's it? You murdered him because you could?
他的死是一种恩惠，而你的死则是胜利
His death was a favor. Yours will be a triumph.
什么鬼…
What the...
对于一个坐在办公室角落里的人来说，你还挺有活力的
You're still pretty spry for a guy with a corner office.
你从不关心霍普
You never cared about Hope.
死的那些，我全不在乎
I don't give a damn about any of them.
弗瑞！来啊
Fury! Come on.
你应该是个杀手？好吧，那就来吧，杀我啊
You're supposed to be a killer? Well, come on, then. Kill me.
哦
Ooh.
你还好吗…
How are you...
别跑，弗瑞
Stop moving, Fury.
你在做什么？我们走吧…
What are you doing? Let's go…
你好像无处不在，啊！
It's like you're everywhere. Aah!
额，那个「野蛮人」是谁?
Uh, what's with the goth kid?
你好，诡计之神
Hello. Trickster God. Hi.
神盾局是一群人
S.H.I.E.L.D. is people,
一群愿意为比为自己更伟大的东西献出生命的人
people willing to give their lives for something greater than themselves
从你这样的人手中拯救世界
to save the world from men like you.
霍普·凡·戴恩特工明白这一点，她会被永远铭记的
Agent Hope Van Dyne understood that and she will never be forgotten.
那你就得尊重她
Then you honor her.
那就表彰她吧
Then honor her.
好吧，这是我的荣幸，弗瑞局长
Well, this was an absolute pleasure, Director Fury.
好，现在拿着你的锤子离开我的星球
Good. Now take your hammer and get off my planet.
关于这一点，我们应该成为盟友
About that, we should be allies.
你知道，我刚刚有个主意
You know, I've just had an idea.
我在想我可能会延长在米德加德的停留时间
I was thinking I might extend my stay here on Midgard.
要多久?
For how long?
星期五
联合国，纽约市
晚上好，我忠诚的臣民们
Good evening, my loyal subjects.
今天站在你们面前，我骄傲的宣布
It is with great pride that I stand before you today
在一天之内
to announce that in just one day's time,
地球上的国家已经把他们的分歧放在一边
the nations of Earth have put aside their differences
在我的指挥下团结一致
and united under my command.
你们渴望被征服，这是人性中不言而喻的事实
It's the unspoken truth of humanity that you crave subjugation.
自由的诱惑阻碍了你，减少了你生活的乐趣
The bright lure of freedom hobbles you, diminishes your life's joy.
你注定要被统治
You were made to be ruled.
所以我来帮助你们完成你们的使命
So I have come to help you fulfill your destiny.
复仇者还没来得及站起来就倒下了
The Avengers fell before they had a chance to rise.
愿他们安息
May they rest in peace.
他们可以，但我们不会
They can, but we won't.
复仇者永远不只是一个团队
The Avengers were always meant to be more than a team.
他们是一个想法
They were an idea,
人类需要相信，在我们最黑暗的时刻
the affirmation of humanity's need to believe that in our darkest hour,
我们会找到我们的英雄
we will find our heroes.
我相信，在这个宇宙中，就像在其他宇宙中一样，希望永不消逝
I believe that in this universe, as in every other, hope never dies.
只要有人把眼光放在大局上
As long as someone keeps their good eye on the bigger picture.
欢迎回来，队长
Welcome back, Captain.
那么，打谁?
So where's the fight?